<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HarmonyHue</string>
    <string name="rules">User Consent and Data Collection: Users must provide explicit consent for the collection of their medical data, including medication history, disease history, gender, sexual orientation, and doctor information. Consent must be obtained through a clear and straightforward process, ensuring users understand what data is being collected and why. Data Protection and Privacy: Compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for users within the EU, ensuring user data is processed lawfully, transparently, and for specific purposes. Adherence to the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) in the USA for the protection of sensitive patient health information. Implementation of robust encryption and security measures to prevent unauthorized access, alteration, or destruction of data. User Rights: Right to access: Users can request access to their personal data stored in the application. Right to rectification: Users have the right to correct any inaccurate or incomplete data. Right to erasure: Users can request the deletion of their personal data under certain conditions. Right to data portability: Users have the right to receive their data in a structured, commonly used format. Data Retention and Use: Data will be retained only as long as necessary for the purposes for which it was collected. Personal data will not be shared with third parties without user consent, except as required by law. Transparency and Accountability: Regular privacy audits and compliance checks to ensure ongoing adherence to both EU and USA regulations. Clear communication channels for users to raise concerns or complaints regarding data handling. Updates to Conditions: The application reserves the right to update these conditions as necessary. Users will be notified of significant changes and must agree to the updated terms to continue using the application. Legal Compliance and Jurisdiction: Compliance with all relevant local, national, and international laws and regulations. Any disputes arising from the use of the application will be subject to the jurisdiction of the courts in the country of registration of the application.</string>
</resources>